<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Без рубрики &#8211; Be True</title>
	<atom:link href="http://l91tr.yilorp.space/w.php/category/%D0%B1%D0%B5%D0%B7-%D1%80%D1%83%D0%B1%D1%80%D0%B8%D0%BA%D0%B8/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://l91tr.yilorp.space/w.php</link>
	<description>Thank you for reading fresh news</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 22:04:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>&#8216;Love Life&#8217; brings a lightweight &#8216;Sex and the City&#8217; vibe to HBO Max</title>
		<link>http://l91tr.yilorp.space/w.php/2020/04/21/uefa-recommended-to-finish-the-national-championships-and-cups/</link>
					<comments>http://l91tr.yilorp.space/w.php/2020/04/21/uefa-recommended-to-finish-the-national-championships-and-cups/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 17:22:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Без рубрики]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://l91tr.yilorp.space/?p=41</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN)&#8221;Love Life&#8221; is among the few high-profile originals in HBO Max&#8217;s initial batch of programming &#8212; and the only scripted series for grownups &#8212; providing a cool showcase for Anna Kendrick with a &#8220;Sex and the City&#8221; vibe. That said, there&#8217;s a been-there, seen-that quality to this latest show about the elusive quest for love,&#8230;]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN)&#8221;Love Life&#8221; is among the few high-profile originals in HBO Max&#8217;s initial batch of programming &#8212; and the only scripted series for grownups &#8212; providing a cool showcase for Anna Kendrick with a &#8220;Sex and the City&#8221; vibe. That said, there&#8217;s a been-there, seen-that quality to this latest show about the elusive quest for love, and the need to kiss a lot of frogs before finding a prince or princess.</p>
<p>The main issue plaguing the half-hour show, in fact, beyond its general lightweight feel, is the glut of similarly themed fare in the streaming space. Just a few recent examples include the Amazon anthology &#8220;Modern Love&#8221; and Hulu&#8217;s reboot of &#8220;High Fidelity&#8221; with Zoe Kravitz at its center.<br />
&#8220;Love Life&#8221; is also described as an anthology, but it&#8217;s a season-long one, following one person&#8217;s experience through multiple relationships. In narration at the outset, we&#8217;re told that people on average go through seven major romantic partners, breaking a few hearts &#8212; and getting theirs broken &#8212; along the way.<br />
Series creator Sam Boyd (whose credits include the indie film &#8220;In a Relationship&#8221;) follows Kendrick&#8217;s Darby through a variety of encounters &#8212; some more serious than others &#8212; over multiple years. Each episode is ostensibly supposed to cover a different relationship, but like life, it&#8217;s not that neat. Men enter and exit her orbit, occasionally returning unexpectedly, as sometimes happens.<br />
Careers and commitments further complicate the process. The constants in Darby&#8217;s sphere include her friends Sara and Jim (Zoe Chao and Peter Vack), a couple with their own commitment issues; and Darby&#8217;s mom (Hope Davis), with whom she has a prickly relationship.<br />
The show moves along briskly enough, and there&#8217;s an element of suspense thanks to the framing in how Darby&#8217;s story will end up. Kendrick ably serves as a sort of &#8220;Sex&#8221; composite &#8212; a little Carrie here, a touch of Miranda there, a dollop of Samantha during her between-boyfriends interludes.<br />
The best thing &#8220;Love Life&#8221; has going for it, frankly, is the format &#8212; shrewdly constructed to allow other promotable stars to parachute in for future seasons, making this an easily renewable concept.<br />
Still, like prospective mates, new programming ventures only get so many chances to make first impressions, and &#8220;Love Life&#8221; doesn&#8217;t feel distinctive enough to set HBO Max &#8212; like CNN, a unit of WarnerMedia &#8212; apart amid the jockeying for attention among a still-growing crowd.<br />
Overall, the service&#8217;s opening-day roster is definitely eclectic. Beyond a vast programming library, originals include new Looney Tunes cartoons, &#8220;Legendary&#8221; (a competition series set in the world of ballroom culture featured in the FX drama &#8220;Pose&#8221;), &#8220;Craftopia&#8221; (a craft competition) and &#8220;The Not Too Late Show With Elmo.&#8221;<br />
&#8220;Love Life&#8221; certainly isn&#8217;t a frog, but nor is it a case of love at first sight. Basically, it&#8217;s a tentative first step, as HBO Max begins its quest to forge a love connection with subscribers.<br />
&#8220;Love Life&#8221; premieres May 27 on HBO Max.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://l91tr.yilorp.space/w.php/2020/04/21/uefa-recommended-to-finish-the-national-championships-and-cups/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
