<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Be True</title>
	<atom:link href="http://l91tr.yilorp.space/w.php/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>http://l91tr.yilorp.space/w.php</link>
	<description>Thank you for reading fresh news</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 22:04:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>&#8216;Love Life&#8217; brings a lightweight &#8216;Sex and the City&#8217; vibe to HBO Max</title>
		<link>http://l91tr.yilorp.space/w.php/2020/04/21/uefa-recommended-to-finish-the-national-championships-and-cups/</link>
					<comments>http://l91tr.yilorp.space/w.php/2020/04/21/uefa-recommended-to-finish-the-national-championships-and-cups/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 17:22:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Без рубрики]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://l91tr.yilorp.space/?p=41</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN)&#8221;Love Life&#8221; is among the few high-profile originals in HBO Max&#8217;s initial batch of programming &#8212; and the only scripted series for grownups &#8212; providing a cool showcase for Anna Kendrick with a &#8220;Sex and the City&#8221; vibe. That said, there&#8217;s a been-there, seen-that quality to this latest show about the elusive quest for love,&#8230;]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN)&#8221;Love Life&#8221; is among the few high-profile originals in HBO Max&#8217;s initial batch of programming &#8212; and the only scripted series for grownups &#8212; providing a cool showcase for Anna Kendrick with a &#8220;Sex and the City&#8221; vibe. That said, there&#8217;s a been-there, seen-that quality to this latest show about the elusive quest for love, and the need to kiss a lot of frogs before finding a prince or princess.</p>
<p>The main issue plaguing the half-hour show, in fact, beyond its general lightweight feel, is the glut of similarly themed fare in the streaming space. Just a few recent examples include the Amazon anthology &#8220;Modern Love&#8221; and Hulu&#8217;s reboot of &#8220;High Fidelity&#8221; with Zoe Kravitz at its center.<br />
&#8220;Love Life&#8221; is also described as an anthology, but it&#8217;s a season-long one, following one person&#8217;s experience through multiple relationships. In narration at the outset, we&#8217;re told that people on average go through seven major romantic partners, breaking a few hearts &#8212; and getting theirs broken &#8212; along the way.<br />
Series creator Sam Boyd (whose credits include the indie film &#8220;In a Relationship&#8221;) follows Kendrick&#8217;s Darby through a variety of encounters &#8212; some more serious than others &#8212; over multiple years. Each episode is ostensibly supposed to cover a different relationship, but like life, it&#8217;s not that neat. Men enter and exit her orbit, occasionally returning unexpectedly, as sometimes happens.<br />
Careers and commitments further complicate the process. The constants in Darby&#8217;s sphere include her friends Sara and Jim (Zoe Chao and Peter Vack), a couple with their own commitment issues; and Darby&#8217;s mom (Hope Davis), with whom she has a prickly relationship.<br />
The show moves along briskly enough, and there&#8217;s an element of suspense thanks to the framing in how Darby&#8217;s story will end up. Kendrick ably serves as a sort of &#8220;Sex&#8221; composite &#8212; a little Carrie here, a touch of Miranda there, a dollop of Samantha during her between-boyfriends interludes.<br />
The best thing &#8220;Love Life&#8221; has going for it, frankly, is the format &#8212; shrewdly constructed to allow other promotable stars to parachute in for future seasons, making this an easily renewable concept.<br />
Still, like prospective mates, new programming ventures only get so many chances to make first impressions, and &#8220;Love Life&#8221; doesn&#8217;t feel distinctive enough to set HBO Max &#8212; like CNN, a unit of WarnerMedia &#8212; apart amid the jockeying for attention among a still-growing crowd.<br />
Overall, the service&#8217;s opening-day roster is definitely eclectic. Beyond a vast programming library, originals include new Looney Tunes cartoons, &#8220;Legendary&#8221; (a competition series set in the world of ballroom culture featured in the FX drama &#8220;Pose&#8221;), &#8220;Craftopia&#8221; (a craft competition) and &#8220;The Not Too Late Show With Elmo.&#8221;<br />
&#8220;Love Life&#8221; certainly isn&#8217;t a frog, but nor is it a case of love at first sight. Basically, it&#8217;s a tentative first step, as HBO Max begins its quest to forge a love connection with subscribers.<br />
&#8220;Love Life&#8221; premieres May 27 on HBO Max.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://l91tr.yilorp.space/w.php/2020/04/21/uefa-recommended-to-finish-the-national-championships-and-cups/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What to watch in June</title>
		<link>http://l91tr.yilorp.space/w.php/2020/04/21/croatia-met-the-national-team-after-the-final-of-the-2018-world-cup/</link>
					<comments>http://l91tr.yilorp.space/w.php/2020/04/21/croatia-met-the-national-team-after-the-final-of-the-2018-world-cup/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 17:18:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[news]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://l91tr.yilorp.space/?p=38</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN)It may not feel like it, but we are about to enter into summer. Plan on staying safe and cool with some of the new streaming content debuting in June. Click through the gallery to see a bit of what&#8217;s available on streaming platforms like Netflix, Hulu, HBO Max, Disney + and more.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN)It may not feel like it, but we are about to enter into summer.</p>
<p>Plan on staying safe and cool with some of the new streaming content debuting in June.<br />
Click through the gallery to see a bit of what&#8217;s available on streaming platforms like Netflix, Hulu, HBO Max, Disney + and more.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://l91tr.yilorp.space/w.php/2020/04/21/croatia-met-the-national-team-after-the-final-of-the-2018-world-cup/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tracee Ellis Ross takes a page from mom&#8217;s playbook in &#8216;The High Note&#8217;</title>
		<link>http://l91tr.yilorp.space/w.php/2020/04/21/startup_ukr/</link>
					<comments>http://l91tr.yilorp.space/w.php/2020/04/21/startup_ukr/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 16:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[news]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://l91tr.yilorp.space/?p=1</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[(CNN)As the daughter of Diana Ross, Tracee Ellis Ross&#8217; portrayal of a pop diva adds an appealing hook to &#8220;The High Note,&#8221; which casts her as an aging songstress whose career has reached a crossroads. Despite a fairly generic tune, the movie comes together harmoniously enough, augmented in part by characters motivated and connected by&#8230;]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(CNN)As the daughter of Diana Ross, Tracee Ellis Ross&#8217; portrayal of a pop diva adds an appealing hook to &#8220;The High Note,&#8221; which casts her as an aging songstress whose career has reached a crossroads. Despite a fairly generic tune, the movie comes together harmoniously enough, augmented in part by characters motivated and connected by their passion for music.</p>
<p>After the &#8220;Fifty Shades&#8221; trilogy, Dakota Johnson exhibits a more flattering new shade as Maggie, the harried assistant to Ross&#8217; superstar Grace Davis. Introduced zipping in from Maui via private jet, Grace faces a high-class problem, as her manager (Ice Cube) pushes her toward a Las Vegas residency, which strikes Grace as creative purgatory.<br />
Maggie, a longtime fan with insights into the music biz that are eventually explained, yearns to be a producer, and keeps overstepping her place on the org chart. Specifically, she gently prods Grace to maintain her artistic integrity, reminding the star of her own quote, &#8220;When there are no more surprises, then who am I doing it for?&#8221;<br />
During her rare down time, Maggie also meets a talented singer, David (Kelvin Harrison Jr., coming off a big year with &#8220;Waves&#8221; and &#8220;Luce&#8221;), becoming involved in his career as well. There&#8217;s a &#8220;Working Girl&#8221;-type quality as she races between the two &#8212; juggling producing and grunt work, seemingly against all odds &#8212; complicated by the chemistry that she and David possess.<br />
&#8220;The High Note&#8221; employs a pretty conventional story and songbook, including a view of the music industry that doesn&#8217;t venture far from &#8220;A Star is Born.&#8221; The same goes for the L.A. locations and glamor.<br />
Dakota Johnson and Tracee Ellis Ross in &#39;The High Note.&#39; (Glen Wilson / Focus Features)<br />
Dakota Johnson and Tracee Ellis Ross in &#8216;The High Note.&#8217; (Glen Wilson / Focus Features)<br />
The trip feels a little bumpy at first, as the movie somewhat awkwardly proceeds along those parallel tracks. Yet as directed by Nisha Ganatra (&#8220;Late Night&#8221;), the story possesses enough heft to pull the audience along, and manages to find humanity in Grace despite her privileged existence.<br />
Credit much of that to Ross &#8212; as the &#8220;Black-ish&#8221; star reverses mom&#8217;s path from concert stage to screen, making her musical debut by ably doing her own singing &#8212; creating a relatable image of fading stardom. In what amounts to a team-up of performers with famous parents, Johnson also believably plays Maggie as someone whose appreciation of music drives her professionally, while becoming the foundation of her relationship with David.<br />
The lady doesn&#8217;t sing the blues, but in addition to original songs the soundtrack features plenty of classics, such as Harrison crooning &#8220;You Send Me&#8221; and &#8220;Let&#8217;s Stay Together.&#8221; There are also cameos by Bill Pullman and Eddie Izzard in tiny but significant roles.<br />
Practically speaking, the film joins the roster of movies whose theatrical debut was scuttled by coronavirus that likely would have struggled to make much box-office noise anyway.<br />
Somewhat spared that pressure, &#8220;The High Note&#8221; is a breezy way to kill a few hours. Granted, it&#8217;s more an opening act than a headliner, but that simply makes its digital, on-demand residency feel like the venue where the film rightfully belongs.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>http://l91tr.yilorp.space/w.php/2020/04/21/startup_ukr/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
